<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>kamefrede.xyz</title><link>http://kamefrede.xyz/</link><description>Recent content on kamefrede.xyz</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Copyright © 2022, Emanuel Ferraz.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 12:16:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://kamefrede.xyz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Global Meet Hotkeys Privacy Policy</title><link>http://kamefrede.xyz/global-meet-hotkeys-privacy-policy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 12:16:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://kamefrede.xyz/global-meet-hotkeys-privacy-policy/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="privacy-policy-for-global-google-meet-hotkeys">Privacy Policy for Global Google Meet Hotkeys&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Effective Date:&lt;/strong> March 4, 2025&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Your privacy is important to us. This Privacy Policy explains what data the Global Google Meet Hotkeys Chrome Extension collects, how it is used, and your rights regarding this data.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h2 id="data-collection-and-usage">Data Collection and Usage&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>The Global Google Meet Hotkeys extension is designed to provide global hotkeys for controlling Google Meet sessions. To achieve this, the extension collects and uses the following data:&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Now</title><link>http://kamefrede.xyz/now/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 22:02:46 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://kamefrede.xyz/now/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="where-am-i-">Where Am I ?&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Still in Porto, Portugal.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="what-am-i-currently-doing">What Am I Currently Doing&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Learning my way around a tambourine, as well as the DAW Bitwig for music production.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Working up the courage to dive into the codebase of &lt;a href="https://github.com/BespokeSynth/BespokeSynth/">Bespoke Synth&lt;/a> and make a PR.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Getting through my book backlog with only one more to go: The Logic of the Soul by Nathaniel Travis.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Watching some of the must-see TV Shows and Movies, currently Twin Peaks (season 1 episode 8).&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="what-am-i-planning-on-doing">What Am I Planning on Doing?&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Post more frequently, or at least not once-a-year.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Planning a follow-up to to &lt;a href="../why-i-stop-doing-things">Why I Stop Doing New Things&lt;/a>, Why I Always Want To Do New Things&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Planning how to approach a blog post on why I ditched strict scheduling and cut down on the hobbies I have.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Planning a retrospective on my tenure as a someone on the organizational side of a folk festival.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>&lt;sup>&lt;sub>Last Updated July 21st 2024&lt;/sub>&lt;/sup>&lt;br>
&lt;sup>&lt;sub>&lt;a href="https://nownownow.com/about">What is this?&lt;/a>&lt;/sub>&lt;/sup>&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Looking Back On 2023</title><link>http://kamefrede.xyz/looking-back-on-2023/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 17:54:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://kamefrede.xyz/looking-back-on-2023/</guid><description>&lt;p>If I had to describe 2023 with one word, it would be stabilization. It had a bit of everything for me, ranging from life-threatening encounters to falling in love (and consequently falling out of love).
Extreme highs but also extreme lows, which managed to balance each other out near the end of the year and reached an equilibrium.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I&amp;rsquo;m grateful for everything that happened, bad and good alike.
Without those experiences, I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t have grown so much.
2023 taught me a lot, and if I were to list it all, this would turn into one hell of a long read, so I&amp;rsquo;m just going to keep it brief.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Reminiscing</title><link>http://kamefrede.xyz/reminiscing/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 15:10:03 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://kamefrede.xyz/reminiscing/</guid><description>&lt;p>Visiting all those places where we dreamed you&amp;rsquo;d be,&lt;br>
Not feeling alone, but there&amp;rsquo;s an absence in me.&lt;br>
I&amp;rsquo;ve made strides since then, and I hope you have too,&lt;br>
Life&amp;rsquo;s path now clearer, confidence anew.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Should fate once again intertwine our two lives,&lt;br>
Let&amp;rsquo;s seize the chance, like old friends who survive.&lt;br>
A toast to the memories, the laughter and tears,&lt;br>
In each story, we&amp;rsquo;ll find echoes of our yesteryears.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Why I Stop Doing Things</title><link>http://kamefrede.xyz/why-i-stop-doing-things/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 15:10:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://kamefrede.xyz/why-i-stop-doing-things/</guid><description>&lt;p>This blog post is a follow-up to &lt;a href="../what-do-i-like">What Do I Like&lt;/a>, in which I talked about how most of the things I do are short-lived, and that I go through phases of intense focus on one activity followed by dropping it for an indeterminate amount of time.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The reason for that? Three words: &lt;strong>fear of failure&lt;/strong>.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I&amp;rsquo;m afraid of failing, afraid of taking risks, afraid of stepping out of my comfort zone, afraid of asking for help, afraid of looking incompetent in the eyes of others.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Fading</title><link>http://kamefrede.xyz/fading/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2021 10:52:44 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://kamefrede.xyz/fading/</guid><description>&lt;p>Under the cherry blossoms my heart rests&lt;br>
longing for someone it has never met.&lt;br>
Waiting for the winds to sweep it away,&lt;br>
Hoping one day it can finally stay.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Wilting as each day slowly passes,&lt;br>
thoughts of a better life close to none.&lt;br>
Constantly comparing itself to the masses,&lt;br>
just to find a disappointment to everyone.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Full of ambitions and aspirations,&lt;br>
aiming for words of validation,&lt;br>
but never able to meet expectations.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Reflection on Mother's Day 2021</title><link>http://kamefrede.xyz/reflection-on-mothers-day-2021/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2021 22:37:44 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://kamefrede.xyz/reflection-on-mothers-day-2021/</guid><description>&lt;p>Today, May 2nd, 2021, here in Portugal we celebrate Mother&amp;rsquo;s Day. It&amp;rsquo;s a time of joy and happiness where you&amp;rsquo;re supposed to show appreciation for your mother and everything she has done for you, or is it?&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I&amp;rsquo;ll preface the rest of this blog post by saying that I love my mother dearly, even if sometimes I seclude myself in my room for days on end, talk back to her or if I&amp;rsquo;m a jerk in general to her. (Here&amp;rsquo;s to you, mom, for putting up with me all these years, even when I didn&amp;rsquo;t deserve it. Thank you for everything, and I hope that I can always be a son who you&amp;rsquo;re proud of)&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Stuff I Enjoy: Minecraft</title><link>http://kamefrede.xyz/stuff-i-enjoy-minecraft/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 13:35:16 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://kamefrede.xyz/stuff-i-enjoy-minecraft/</guid><description>&lt;p>Welcome to the first installment of Stuff I Enjoy! I was going to postpone this to next week but decided against it.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This installment is dedicated to Minecraft, a game that shaped my entire youth. I started playing Minecraft in 2011, around the time that Beta 1.7.3 dropped. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t until Beta 1.8 that I actually started getting more into it.
Why? When I first booted it up, I created a survival world but didn&amp;rsquo;t know how to break blocks. I was trying to get wood by spam clicking it instead of holding the mouse button. Which, in hindsight, doesn&amp;rsquo;t make sense at all, but younger me thought it was the way to do it and was so confused that it wasn&amp;rsquo;t working to the point of closing the game in a fit of anger.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>What Do I Like</title><link>http://kamefrede.xyz/what-do-i-like/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2021 14:59:58 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://kamefrede.xyz/what-do-i-like/</guid><description>&lt;p>Lately, I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to get into writing more. My friends Adrian, Alwinfy, and Willie encouraged me to start writing blog posts as it would be a decent way to get started. I thought about it for a while and concluded that they were right. Taking up blogging would be nice. But then, I ran into my first blocker. What would I write?&lt;/p>
&lt;p>My first instinct was to do some online searching about it, as it was unlikely that I was the only person who didn&amp;rsquo;t know what to blog.
The answer that showed up pretty much everywhere was to write about what you like. I gave it a lot of thought, but I couldn&amp;rsquo;t come up with anything. At this point, you, the reader, might be thinking, how is it possible that he doesn&amp;rsquo;t know what he likes?&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>http://kamefrede.xyz/contact/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 20:03:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://kamefrede.xyz/contact/</guid><description>&lt;p>I&amp;rsquo;m pretty light on social media nowadays, if you feel the need to stalk me or somehow get ahold of me, you have plenty of options below!&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="contact--social-links">Contact &amp;amp; Social Links&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Discord&lt;/strong>: &lt;a href="https://discordapp.com/users/66151783960948736">kamefrede&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>GitHub&lt;/strong>: &lt;a href="https://github.com/YourGitHubUsername">kamefrede&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Email&lt;/strong>: &lt;a href="mailto:kamefrede@gmail.com">kamefrede&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>LinkedIn&lt;/strong>: &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/kamefrede/">Emanuel Ferraz&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h4 id="personal-profiles">Personal Profiles&lt;/h4>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Serializd&lt;/strong>: &lt;a href="https://serializd.com/user/emanuelmf">emanuelmf&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Backloggd&lt;/strong>: &lt;a href="https://www.backloggd.com/u/kamefrede">kamefrede&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Letterboxd&lt;/strong>: &lt;a href="https://letterboxd.com/emanuelmf">emanuelmf&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Goodreads&lt;/strong>: &lt;a href="https://www.goodreads.com/user/show/79587478-emanuel-ferraz">Emanuel Ferraz&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>MyAnimeList&lt;/strong>: &lt;a href="https://myanimelist.net/profile/kamefrede">kamefrede&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>About</title><link>http://kamefrede.xyz/about/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 19:48:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://kamefrede.xyz/about/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="who-am-i">Who am I?&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Greetings!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>My name is Emanuel Ferraz, better known on the internet as Kamefrede.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="what-do-you-do">What do you do?&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>I&amp;rsquo;m a backend engineer (in job title only, I have no formal engineering degree) at Uphold.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="where-are-you-based">Where are you based?&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>In the lovely city of Porto in Portugal.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="when-did-you-start-this-blog">When did you start this blog?&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>2021, in the middle of the Global Event.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="why-did-you-create-this-blog">Why did you create this blog?&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Honestly? I saw that my friend &lt;a href="https://vincent-lee.net">williewillus&lt;/a> had one, and I thought it&amp;rsquo;d be cool to have one myself.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Hello Internet</title><link>http://kamefrede.xyz/hello-internet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 19:48:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://kamefrede.xyz/hello-internet/</guid><description>&lt;p>After much delaying, I finally caved in and set up a website for real.
This is my 3rd attempt at a website, I think.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The first attempt went badly since I was trying to minimize the use of Javascript but I still wanted to have fancy animations and navbars and whatnot.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>For my second attempt I realized that I didn&amp;rsquo;t need any of that fanciness and was recommended by my friend &lt;a href="https://vincent-lee.net">Williewillus&lt;/a> to check out both Jekyll and Hugo.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>