<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>kamefrede.xyz</title><link>http://kamefrede.xyz/</link><description>Recent content on kamefrede.xyz</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Copyright © 2022, Emanuel Ferraz.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 22:02:46 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://kamefrede.xyz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Now</title><link>http://kamefrede.xyz/now/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 22:02:46 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://kamefrede.xyz/now/</guid><description>Where Am I ? Still in Porto, Portugal.
What Am I Currently Doing Trying to do clean-up of all the tech drawers. In addition to doing physical cleaning I am also drilling down on the hobbies that truly matter to me.
Could be an interesting follow-up to Why I Stop Doing New Things, Why I Always Want To Do New Things Learning my way around a tambourine, as well as the DAW Bitwig for music production.</description></item><item><title>Looking Back On 2023</title><link>http://kamefrede.xyz/looking-back-on-2023/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 17:54:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://kamefrede.xyz/looking-back-on-2023/</guid><description>If I had to describe 2023 with one word, it would be stabilization. It had a bit of everything for me, ranging from life-threatening encounters to falling in love (and consequently falling out of love). Extreme highs but also extreme lows, which managed to balance each other out near the end of the year and reached an equilibrium.
I&amp;rsquo;m grateful for everything that happened, bad and good alike. Without those experiences, I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t have grown so much.</description></item><item><title>Reminiscing</title><link>http://kamefrede.xyz/reminiscing/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 15:10:03 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://kamefrede.xyz/reminiscing/</guid><description>Visiting all those places where we dreamed you&amp;rsquo;d be,
Not feeling alone, but there&amp;rsquo;s an absence in me.
I&amp;rsquo;ve made strides since then, and I hope you have too,
Life&amp;rsquo;s path now clearer, confidence anew.
Should fate once again intertwine our two lives,
Let&amp;rsquo;s seize the chance, like old friends who survive.
A toast to the memories, the laughter and tears,
In each story, we&amp;rsquo;ll find echoes of our yesteryears.</description></item><item><title>Why I Stop Doing Things</title><link>http://kamefrede.xyz/why-i-stop-doing-things/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 15:10:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://kamefrede.xyz/why-i-stop-doing-things/</guid><description>This blog post is a follow-up to What Do I Like, in which I talked about how most of the things I do are short-lived, and that I go through phases of intense focus on one activity followed by dropping it for an indeterminate amount of time.
The reason for that? Three words: fear of failure.
I&amp;rsquo;m afraid of failing, afraid of taking risks, afraid of stepping out of my comfort zone, afraid of asking for help, afraid of looking incompetent in the eyes of others.</description></item><item><title>Fading</title><link>http://kamefrede.xyz/fading/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2021 10:52:44 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://kamefrede.xyz/fading/</guid><description>Under the cherry blossoms my heart rests
longing for someone it has never met.
Waiting for the winds to sweep it away,
Hoping one day it can finally stay.
Wilting as each day slowly passes,
thoughts of a better life close to none.
Constantly comparing itself to the masses,
just to find a disappointment to everyone.
Full of ambitions and aspirations,
aiming for words of validation,
but never able to meet expectations.</description></item><item><title>Reflection on Mother's Day 2021</title><link>http://kamefrede.xyz/reflection-on-mothers-day-2021/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2021 22:37:44 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://kamefrede.xyz/reflection-on-mothers-day-2021/</guid><description>Today, May 2nd, 2021, here in Portugal we celebrate Mother&amp;rsquo;s Day. It&amp;rsquo;s a time of joy and happiness where you&amp;rsquo;re supposed to show appreciation for your mother and everything she has done for you, or is it?
I&amp;rsquo;ll preface the rest of this blog post by saying that I love my mother dearly, even if sometimes I seclude myself in my room for days on end, talk back to her or if I&amp;rsquo;m a jerk in general to her.</description></item><item><title>Stuff I Enjoy: Minecraft</title><link>http://kamefrede.xyz/stuff-i-enjoy-minecraft/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 13:35:16 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://kamefrede.xyz/stuff-i-enjoy-minecraft/</guid><description>Welcome to the first installment of Stuff I Enjoy! I was going to postpone this to next week but decided against it.
This installment is dedicated to Minecraft, a game that shaped my entire youth. I started playing Minecraft in 2011, around the time that Beta 1.7.3 dropped. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t until Beta 1.8 that I actually started getting more into it. Why? When I first booted it up, I created a survival world but didn&amp;rsquo;t know how to break blocks.</description></item><item><title>What Do I Like</title><link>http://kamefrede.xyz/what-do-i-like/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2021 14:59:58 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://kamefrede.xyz/what-do-i-like/</guid><description>Lately, I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to get into writing more. My friends Adrian, Alwinfy, and Willie encouraged me to start writing blog posts as it would be a decent way to get started. I thought about it for a while and concluded that they were right. Taking up blogging would be nice. But then, I ran into my first blocker. What would I write?
My first instinct was to do some online searching about it, as it was unlikely that I was the only person who didn&amp;rsquo;t know what to blog.</description></item><item><title>Games</title><link>http://kamefrede.xyz/games/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 20:03:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://kamefrede.xyz/games/</guid><description>Index Index Completed games Playing Dropped To Play Inspired by my friend Williewillus every time I finish a game from today (November 20th 2020) onwards I will post a short review on my blog and update the table below with a the review score and a link to the review. (Keep in mind I will not retroactively add past played games since that would be a huge chore)
Completed games Name Genres Platform Rating /10 Unreal Life Adventure PC 8 Katana Zero Platformer Switch 10 Detective Case and Clown Bot Point &amp;amp; Click, Detective PC 7 Gunpoint Stealth, Puzzle, Detective PC 8 Eliza Story PC 8 Red Strings Club PC 7 Evan&amp;rsquo;s Remains Puzzle, Story PC 7 Playing Name Platform CrossCode Switch Hotline Miami PC Ghostrunner PC Dropped Name Platform Okami HD PC Yoshi&amp;rsquo;s Crafted World Switch Yakuza Zero PC To Play Name Platform Divinity Original Sin 2 PC Dead Cells Switch Borderlands PC Wizard of Legend Switch Disco Elysium PC Tyranny PC Narita Boy Switch Elden Ring PC Octopath Traveller Switch Pokemon Brilliant Diamond Switch Hades Switch Transistor Switch Link&amp;rsquo;s Awakening Switch</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>http://kamefrede.xyz/about/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 19:48:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://kamefrede.xyz/about/</guid><description>Who am I? Greetings!
My name is Emanuel Ferraz, better known on the internet as Kamefrede.
What do you do? I&amp;rsquo;m a backend engineer (in job title only, I have no formal engineering degree) at Uphold.
Where are you based? In the lovely city of Porto in Portugal.
When did you start this blog? 2021, in the middle of the Global Event.
Why did you create this blog? Honestly? I saw that my friend williewillus had one, and I thought it&amp;rsquo;d be cool to have one myself.</description></item><item><title>Hello Internet</title><link>http://kamefrede.xyz/hello-internet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 19:48:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://kamefrede.xyz/hello-internet/</guid><description>After much delaying, I finally caved in and set up a website for real. This is my 3rd attempt at a website, I think.
The first attempt went badly since I was trying to minimize the use of Javascript but I still wanted to have fancy animations and navbars and whatnot.
For my second attempt I realized that I didn&amp;rsquo;t need any of that fanciness and was recommended by my friend Williewillus to check out both Jekyll and Hugo.</description></item></channel></rss>