<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>kamefrede.xyz</title><link>http://kamefrede.xyz/</link><description>Recent content on kamefrede.xyz</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Copyright © 2020, Emanuel Ferraz.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 13:35:16 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://kamefrede.xyz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Stuff I Enjoy Mc Pt1</title><link>http://kamefrede.xyz/stuff-i-enjoy-mc-pt1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 13:35:16 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://kamefrede.xyz/stuff-i-enjoy-mc-pt1/</guid><description>Welcome to the first installment of Stuff I Enjoy! I was going to postpone this to next week but decided against it.
This installment is dedicated to Minecraft, a game that shaped my entire youth. I started playing Minecraft in 2011, around the time that Beta 1.7.3 dropped. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t until Beta 1.8 that I actually started getting more into it. Why? When I first booted it up, I created a survival world but didn&amp;rsquo;t know how to break blocks.</description></item><item><title>What Do I Like</title><link>http://kamefrede.xyz/what-do-i-like/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2021 14:59:58 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://kamefrede.xyz/what-do-i-like/</guid><description>Lately, I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to get into writing more. My friends Adrian, Alwinfy, and Willie encouraged me to start writing blog posts as it would be a decent way to get started. I thought about it for a while and concluded that they were right. Taking up blogging would be nice. But then, I ran into my first blocker. What would I write?
My first instinct was to do some online searching about it, as it was unlikely that I was the only person who didn&amp;rsquo;t know what to blog.</description></item><item><title>Games</title><link>http://kamefrede.xyz/games/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 20:03:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://kamefrede.xyz/games/</guid><description>Index Completed Currently playing Dropped To play Inspired by my friend Williewillus every time I finish a game from today (November 20th 2020) onwards I will post a short review on my blog and update the table below with a the review score and a link to the review. (Keep in mind I will not retroactively add past played games since that would be a huge chore)
Completed games Name Platform Genres Rating /10 Unreal Life Adventure 8 Currently Playing Name Platform Yakuza Zero PC Adventures to Go PSP Kingdom Hearts: Birth by Sleep PSP Kirby Nightmare in Dreamland GBA Phoenix Wright: Ace Attorney NDS The World Ends With You NDS Legend of Zelda: Breath of the Wild Switch Yoshi&amp;rsquo;s Crafted World Switch Dropped Name Platform Okami HD PC To Play Name Platform</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>http://kamefrede.xyz/about/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 19:48:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://kamefrede.xyz/about/</guid><description>Who am I? Hi!
My name is Emanuel Ferraz, better known on the internet as Kamefrede. I&amp;rsquo;m a software developer from Gondomar, Portugal.
What kind of software do you develop? In my day job, I mostly maintain legacy codebases(mostly C# and JS) and develop tailor-made software for various different clients(factories, restaurants, etc..).
In my spare time, I mostly do Minecraft modding in both Java and Kotlin(I was going to try Clojure, but it was too much of a pain to get it to work).</description></item><item><title>Hello Internet</title><link>http://kamefrede.xyz/hello-internet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 19:48:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://kamefrede.xyz/hello-internet/</guid><description>After much delaying, I finally caved in and set up a website for real. This is my 3rd attempt at a website, I think.
The first attempt went badly since I was trying to minimize the use of Javascript but I still wanted to have fancy animations and navbars and whatnot.
For my second attempt I realized that I didn&amp;rsquo;t need any of that fanciness and was recommended by my friend Williewillus to check out both Jekyll and Hugo.</description></item></channel></rss>