<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Reflection on kamefrede.xyz</title><link>http://kamefrede.xyz/blog/reflection/</link><description>Recent content in Reflection on kamefrede.xyz</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Copyright © 2025, Emanuel Ferraz.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 17:54:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://kamefrede.xyz/blog/reflection/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Looking Back On 2023</title><link>http://kamefrede.xyz/looking-back-on-2023/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 17:54:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://kamefrede.xyz/looking-back-on-2023/</guid><description>&lt;p>If I had to describe 2023 with one word, it would be stabilization. It had a bit of everything for me, ranging from life-threatening encounters to falling in love (and consequently falling out of love).
Extreme highs but also extreme lows, which managed to balance each other out near the end of the year and reached an equilibrium.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I&amp;rsquo;m grateful for everything that happened, bad and good alike.
Without those experiences, I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t have grown so much.
2023 taught me a lot, and if I were to list it all, this would turn into one hell of a long read, so I&amp;rsquo;m just going to keep it brief.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Reflection on Mother's Day 2021</title><link>http://kamefrede.xyz/reflection-on-mothers-day-2021/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2021 22:37:44 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://kamefrede.xyz/reflection-on-mothers-day-2021/</guid><description>&lt;p>Today, May 2nd, 2021, here in Portugal we celebrate Mother&amp;rsquo;s Day. It&amp;rsquo;s a time of joy and happiness where you&amp;rsquo;re supposed to show appreciation for your mother and everything she has done for you, or is it?&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I&amp;rsquo;ll preface the rest of this blog post by saying that I love my mother dearly, even if sometimes I seclude myself in my room for days on end, talk back to her or if I&amp;rsquo;m a jerk in general to her. (Here&amp;rsquo;s to you, mom, for putting up with me all these years, even when I didn&amp;rsquo;t deserve it. Thank you for everything, and I hope that I can always be a son who you&amp;rsquo;re proud of)&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>