<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>sie on kamefrede.xyz</title><link>http://kamefrede.xyz/blog/sie/</link><description>Recent content in sie on kamefrede.xyz</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Copyright © 2022, Emanuel Ferraz.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 15:10:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://kamefrede.xyz/blog/sie/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Why I Stop Doing Things</title><link>http://kamefrede.xyz/why-i-stop-doing-things/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 15:10:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://kamefrede.xyz/why-i-stop-doing-things/</guid><description>This blog post is a follow-up to What Do I Like, in which I talked about how most of the things I do are short-lived, and that I go through phases of intense focus on one activity followed by dropping it for an indeterminate amount of time.
The reason for that? Three words: fear of failure.
I&amp;rsquo;m afraid of failing, afraid of taking risks, afraid of stepping out of my comfort zone, afraid of asking for help, afraid of looking incompetent in the eyes of others.</description></item><item><title>Stuff I Enjoy Mc Pt1</title><link>http://kamefrede.xyz/stuff-i-enjoy-mc-pt1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 13:35:16 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://kamefrede.xyz/stuff-i-enjoy-mc-pt1/</guid><description>Welcome to the first installment of Stuff I Enjoy! I was going to postpone this to next week but decided against it.
This installment is dedicated to Minecraft, a game that shaped my entire youth. I started playing Minecraft in 2011, around the time that Beta 1.7.3 dropped. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t until Beta 1.8 that I actually started getting more into it. Why? When I first booted it up, I created a survival world but didn&amp;rsquo;t know how to break blocks.</description></item><item><title>What Do I Like</title><link>http://kamefrede.xyz/what-do-i-like/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2021 14:59:58 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://kamefrede.xyz/what-do-i-like/</guid><description>Lately, I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to get into writing more. My friends Adrian, Alwinfy, and Willie encouraged me to start writing blog posts as it would be a decent way to get started. I thought about it for a while and concluded that they were right. Taking up blogging would be nice. But then, I ran into my first blocker. What would I write?
My first instinct was to do some online searching about it, as it was unlikely that I was the only person who didn&amp;rsquo;t know what to blog.</description></item></channel></rss>